<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-04-04T08:08:39+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>The academic profile of Prof. O-Joun Lee at The Catholic University of Korea </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Van Thuy Hoang won the Best Award in the 22nd Graduate School Academic Awards</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/van-thuy-hoang-won-the-best-award-in-the-22nd-graduate-school-academic-awards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Van Thuy Hoang won the Best Award in the 22nd Graduate School Academic Awards"/><published>2025-03-10T03:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-03-10T03:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/van-thuy-hoang-won-the-best-award-in-the-22nd-graduate-school-academic-awards</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/van-thuy-hoang-won-the-best-award-in-the-22nd-graduate-school-academic-awards/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Catholic University of Korea (CUK) announced that Van Thuy Hoang, a Ph.D. candidate in the Department of Artificial Intelligence, has been awarded the Best Award (최우수상) at the 22nd Graduate School Academic Awards (제22회 대학원 학술상) Ceremony. Mr. Hoang was recognized for his outstanding research achievements in the field of graph learning and recommendation systems​. This prestigious honor highlights the excellence of his work and his significant contributions to advancing artificial intelligence at CUK and beyond. Mr. Hoang’s research focuses on graph-based machine learning, where he has developed novel graph neural network models that push the boundaries of graph representation learning. Notably, his work introduced the “Unified Graph Transformer,” a model that effectively integrates local and global network information to learn powerful graph representations. This approach achieved state-of-the-art performance on numerous benchmark datasets​ and was presented at the AAAI 2024 conference, underscoring the impact and international recognition of his research​. In addition, he has applied graph learning to intelligent recommendation systems, designing knowledge graph-driven frameworks for real-world applications – for example, a halal cosmetic recommendation system that leverages complex relationships between products and ingredients to improve cultural relevance in recommendations​. At the 22nd Graduate School Academic Awards Ceremony, Mr. Hoang’s accomplishments earned the event’s top honor, the Best Award. This award is bestowed on the most distinguished graduate research contributions, and Mr. Hoang’s selection reflects the high esteem in which his work is held within the academic community. The recognition not only celebrates his individual excellence but also emphasizes the importance of graph-based AI research as a critical area of innovation at CUK. Mr. Hoang’s success serves as an inspiration to fellow researchers and highlights the growing impact of artificial intelligence and network science in addressing complex real-world challenges. As the home of this achievement, CUK’s Network Science Lab has established itself as a leader in graph-based AI and machine learning research. Under the guidance of Prof. O-Joun Lee, the lab has pioneered cutting-edge graph learning methodologies and applied them to real-world domains, covering innovations such as advanced recommendation systems for offline retail environments​ and novel graph neural network models for molecular structure learning in chemistry​. The lab’s comprehensive approach – bridging theoretical innovation with interdisciplinary collaboration – demonstrates how graph learning can drive the next generation of AI solutions. Together, Mr. Hoang and the Network Science Lab are shaping the future of AI, exemplifying innovation and impact through network science.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">One NS-CUK paper presented at AAAI’25</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/one-ns-cuk-paper-presented-at-aaai25/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="One NS-CUK paper presented at AAAI’25"/><published>2025-02-28T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-02-28T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/one-ns-cuk-paper-presented-at-aaai25</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/one-ns-cuk-paper-presented-at-aaai25/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team member, Van Thuy Hoang, presented his paper, which is titled “Pre-training Graph Neural Networks on Molecules by using Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck” and depicts his novel molecular graph neural network pre-training method called “Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck (S-CGIB),” at the 39th AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2025). This recognition demonstrated his dedication and expertise in graph learning. Van Thuy Hoang, O-Joun Lee: Pre-training Graph Neural Networks on Molecules by using Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck. The 39th AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2025), Philadelphia, PA, USA; 02/2025.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Halal or Not, A Novel GNN Model for Predicting Cultural Appropriateness of Everyday Products</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/halal-or-not-a-novel-gnn-model-for-predicting-cultural-appropriateness-of-everyday-products/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Halal or Not, A Novel GNN Model for Predicting Cultural Appropriateness of Everyday Products"/><published>2025-01-08T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-01-08T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/halal-or-not-a-novel-gnn-model-for-predicting-cultural-appropriateness-of-everyday-products</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2025/halal-or-not-a-novel-gnn-model-for-predicting-cultural-appropriateness-of-everyday-products/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We present HaCKG, a novel GNN model for analyzing ingredients of everyday products to predict their cultural availability, e.g. predicting whether food or cosmetics meet halal or vegan criteria. HaCKG is developed by NS Lab, CUK, based on pure PyTorch backend. The overall architecture of LiteralKG. The growing demand for halal cosmetic products has exposed significant challenges, especially in Muslimmajority countries. Recently, various machine learning-based strategies, e.g., image-based methods, have shown remarkable success in predicting the halal status of cosmetics. However, these methods mainly focus on analyzing the discrete and specific ingredients within separate cosmetics, which ignore the high-order and complex relations between cosmetics and ingredients. To address this problem, we propose a halal cosmetic recommendation framework, namely HaCKG, that leverages a knowledge graph of cosmetics and their ingredients to explicitly model and capture the relationships between cosmetics and their components. By representing cosmetics and ingredients as entities within the knowledge graph, HaCKG effectively learns the high-order and complex relations between entities, offering a robust method for predicting halal status. Specifically, we first construct a cosmetic knowledge graph representing the relations between various cosmetics, ingredients, and their properties. We then propose a pre-trained relational graph attention network model with residual connections to learn the structural relation between entities in the knowledge graph. The pre-trained model is then fine-tuned on downstream cosmetic data to predict halal status. Extensive experiments on the cosmetic dataset over halal prediction tasks demonstrate the superiority of our model over state-of-the-art baselines. A short description of HaCKG: We construct a cosmetic knowledge graph that represents the natural relations between cosmetic products, ingredients, and the ingredient’s properties. The knowledge graph then can serve as a fundamental tool for our model to learn cosmetic relations and predict the halal status. The main core of HaCKG is a pre-trained residual Graph Attention Network (r-GAT) that incorporates residual connections to capture relationships between entities in the cosmetic knowledge graph effectively in the context of Self-Supervised Learning. The pre-training strategy enables r-GAT to learn the structural relationships among cosmetics, ingredients, and their properties without relying on label information. We conduct extensive experiments on halal cosmetic product datasets. The significant improvements demonstrate the superiority of our proposed model compared to state-of-the-art baselines. The HaCKG is available at: Cite “HaCKG” as: Please cite our paper if you find HaCKG useful in your work: @Article{Hoang2023, author={Van Thuy Hoang and Tien-Bach-Thanh Do and Jinho Seo and Seung Charlie Kim and Luong Vuong Nguyen and Duong Nguyen Minh Huy and Hyeon-Ju Jeon and O-Joun Lee}, title={Halal or Not: Knowledge Graph Completion for Predicting Cultural Appropriateness of Daily Products}, journal={IEEE Access}, year={2025}, volume={}, pages={}, month=jan, issn={2169-3536}, doi={10.1109/ACCESS.2025.3528488}, } :page_facing_up::woman_technologist::bookmark_tabs::label::black_nib: Contributors:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">S-CGIB, A Novel Pre-trained Graph Neural Network Model in Molecular Structure Learning</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/s-cgib-a-novel-pre-trained-graph-neural-network-model-in-molecular-structure-learning/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="S-CGIB, A Novel Pre-trained Graph Neural Network Model in Molecular Structure Learning"/><published>2024-12-19T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-19T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/s-cgib-a-novel-pre-trained-graph-neural-network-model-in-molecular-structure-learning</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/s-cgib-a-novel-pre-trained-graph-neural-network-model-in-molecular-structure-learning/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We present S-CGIB, a novel Architecture for Pre-training Graph Neural Networks in Molecular Structure Learning and developed by NS Lab, CUK based on pure PyTorch backend. The paper has been accepted for presentation at the AAAI 2025 conference. The overall architecture of Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck. We aim to build a pre-trained Graph Neural Network (GNN) model on molecules without human annotations or prior knowledge. Although various attempts have been proposed to overcome limitations in acquiring labeled molecules, the previous pre-training methods still rely on semantic subgraphs, i.e., functional groups. Only focusing on the functional groups could overlook the graph-level distinctions. The key challenge to build a pre-trained GNN on molecules is how to (1) generate well-distinguished graph-level representations and (2) automatically discover the functional groups without prior knowledge. To solve it, we propose a novel Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck, named S-CGIB, for pre-training GNNs to recognize core subgraphs (graph cores) and significant subgraphs. The main idea is that the graph cores contain compressed and sufficient information that could generate well-distinguished graph-level representations and reconstruct the input graph conditioned on significant subgraphs across molecules under the S-CGIB principle. To discover significant subgraphs without prior knowledge about functional groups, we propose generating a set of functional group candidates, i.e., ego networks, and using an attention-based interaction between the graph core and the candidates. Despite being identified from self-supervised learning, our learned subgraphs match the real-world functional groups. Extensive experiments on molecule datasets across various domains demonstrate the superiority of S-CGIB. A short description of S-CGIB: S-CGIB is trained to generate well-distinguished graph-level representations and automatically capture significant subgraphs without explicit annotations or prior knowledge in the context of Self-Supervised Learning. The fundamental idea behind our strategy is that, across the chemical domain, molecules share universal core subgraphs that can combine with specific significant subgraphs to robust representations of molecules. S-CGIB generates well-distinguished graph-level representations by compressing an input molecule graph into a graph core conditioned on specific significant subgraphs without using label information under the Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck principle. S-CGIB discover the significant subgraphs (functional groups) from the subgraph candidates (ego networks rooted at each node) through the attention-based interaction between the graph core and the ego networks under the graph reconstruction. Extensive experiments on molecule datasets across four domains demonstrate the superiority of S-CGIB. The S-CGIB is available at: Cite “S-CGIB” as: Please cite our paper if you find S-CGIB useful in your work: @misc{hoang2024pretraininggraphneuralnetworks, title={Pre-training Graph Neural Networks on Molecules by Using Subgraph-Conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck}, author={Van Thuy Hoang and O-Joun Lee}, year={2024}, eprint={2412.15589}, archivePrefix={arXiv}, primaryClass={cs.LG}, url={https://arxiv.org/abs/2412.15589}, } :page_facing_up::woman_technologist::bookmark_tabs::label::black_nib: Contributors:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">One NS-CUK paper accepted for AAAI’25</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/one-ns-cuk-paper-accepted-for-aaai25/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="One NS-CUK paper accepted for AAAI’25"/><published>2024-12-09T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-09T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/one-ns-cuk-paper-accepted-for-aaai25</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/one-ns-cuk-paper-accepted-for-aaai25/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, NS-CUK successfully submitted one research paper to the AAAI, which is one of the most prestigious conferences in AI fields, and was accepted. This paper, accepted into the main technical track, presents a novel method for pre-training graph neural networks on molecules. Details of this paper are as follows: Van Thuy Hoang, O-Joun Lee: Pre-training Graph Neural Networks on Molecules by using Subgraph-conditioned Graph Information Bottleneck. The 39th AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2025), Philadelphia, PA, USA; 02/2025.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jin Woo Jeong and Ju Hee Shim won the Best Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on AI, CSIE, and DS</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-and-ju-hee-shim-won-the-best-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-ai-csie-and-ds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jin Woo Jeong and Ju Hee Shim won the Best Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on AI, CSIE, and DS"/><published>2024-11-11T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-11T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-and-ju-hee-shim-won-the-best-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-ai-csie-and-ds</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-and-ju-hee-shim-won-the-best-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-ai-csie-and-ds/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The undergraduate research assistants of NS Lab@CUK, Jin Woo Jeong and Ju Hee Shim, have excelled in the 2024 CUK Competition on AI, CSIE, and DS (제 3회 가톨릭대학교 인공지능학과/컴퓨터정보공학부/데이터사이언스학과 경진대회) and won the best award. Jin Woo Jeong and Ju Hee Shim developed a trajectory recommendation model for personalized tours in Bucheon.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2024 Fall CUK AI Seminar Series</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/2024-fall-cuk-ai-seminar-series/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2024 Fall CUK AI Seminar Series"/><published>2024-08-24T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-24T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/2024-fall-cuk-ai-seminar-series</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/2024-fall-cuk-ai-seminar-series/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Fall CUK Artificial Intelligence Seminar Series (2024년 가을 가톨릭대학교 인공지능 세미나) The Department of AI at CUK is hosting a seminar series focusing on diverse application domains of artificial intelligence. Spanning 13 weeks, from September 3rd, 2024, to November 26th, 2024, this series will feature 11 talks by leading experts from both the corporate world and research institutions. Details of the seminar series are as follows: Location: Sophie Barat Hall B351, Songsim Global Campus, The Catholic University of Korea Time: Tuesdays, 18:00 Assistant: TBA Programme at a glance Sep 3rd, 2024 - KIAPS(차세대수치예보모델개발사업단) 전현주 연구원: 인공지능을 활용한 기상예측 Sep 10th, 2024 - 딥앤하이 김도현 대표: 인공지능의, 인공지능에 의한, 인공지능을 위한 교육 - 교육업계를 바꾸는 AI바람 Sep 24th, 2024 - 무브먼츠 이종서 연구소장: 스마트 건설 기술을 활용한 토목 분야 기술 개발 및 적용 현황 Oct 1st, 2024 - 모어사이언스 송영조 박사: 과학커뮤니케이터가 설명해주는 어메이징 브레인쇼 Oct 8th, 2024 - 삼성 리서치 김경래 박사: 오디오-비전 멀티모달 기술의 활용 Oct 22nd, 2024 - 포엔 김성균 대표: 의료인공지능과 설명가능인공지능 Oct 29th, 2024 - 고려대학교 세종 지능형반도체공학과 정성엽 교수: 인공지능 기반 반도체 설계 기술 Nov 5th, 2024 - 슈크란 코리아 김승 대표: 온라인 리테일 상품의 문화적 가용성 예측 기술 Nov 12th, 2024 - 가우스랩스 이재한 박사: 산업 분야에서 활용되는 이상 검출 및 지역화 기술 연구 동향과 전망 Nov 19th, 2024 - 삼성전자 종합기술원 (SAIT) 진동권 박사: 자율주행을 위한 딥러닝 기반의 차선 검출 기술 Nov 26th, 2024 - 삼성전자 MX 사업부 김지수 박사: 증강 현실을 위한 영상 처리 기술 Past events The 2024 Fall CUK Artificial Intelligence Seminar Series The 2024 Spring CUK Artificial Intelligence Seminar Series The 2023 Fall CUK Artificial Intelligence Seminar Series The 2023 Spring CUK Artificial Intelligence Seminar Series]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jin Woo Jeong won the Encouragement Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on Industrial Mathematics</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-industrial-mathematics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jin Woo Jeong won the Encouragement Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on Industrial Mathematics"/><published>2024-06-07T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-06-07T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-industrial-mathematics</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-industrial-mathematics/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The undergraduate research assistant of NS Lab@CUK, Jin Woo Jeong, has excelled in the 2024 CUK Competition on Industrial Mathematics (제1회 가톨릭대학교 수학과 산업수학 경진대회) and won the encouragement award. Jin Woo Jeong developed a model to predict the KOSPI index for the next 20 days using LSTM.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">NS-CUK Summer School on Digital Humanities 2024</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/ns-cuk-summer-school-on-digital-humanities-2024/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NS-CUK Summer School on Digital Humanities 2024"/><published>2024-05-21T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-21T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/ns-cuk-summer-school-on-digital-humanities-2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/ns-cuk-summer-school-on-digital-humanities-2024/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2nd NS-CUK Summer School on Digital Humanities: Where ‘Humanities’ and ‘Technology’ Meet (NS-CUK DH 2024) 2024년 가톨릭대학교 디지털인문학 여름학교: ‘인문학’과 ‘기술’이 만나는 곳 NS Lab@CUK organizes a summer school dedicated to digital humanities. This program consists of 10 lectures presented by Dr. Eun-Soon You (유은순 박사) and is scheduled to take place over a period of three weeks, from July 17th, 2024, to July 31st, 2024. A world where humanities, technology, and arts communicate, digital humanities guide you into the realm of fusion. While humanities explore the essence of humanity, digital humanities transform that exploration into data and connect it to the future. Experience new insights into humanity and technology this summer at the Digital Humanities Special Lecture! 인문학과 기술 그리고 예술이 소통하는 세계, 디지털 인문학이 여러분을 융합의 세계로 안내합니다. 인문학이 인간의 본질을 탐구한다면 디지털 인문학은 그 탐구를 데이터로 만들어 미래로 연결합니다. 올여름 디지털 인문학 특강에서 인간과 기술에 대한 새로운 통찰을 경험하세요! Here are the details of the summer school: Location: Sophie Barat Hall B351, Songsim Global Campus, The Catholic University of Korea Time: July 17th (Wed) to July 31st (Wed), 13:00 – 15:00 Speaker: Dr. Eun-Soon You, Department of Artificial Intelligence, CUK Contact: Prof. O-Joun Lee, Department of Artificial Intelligence, CUK TA: TBA Registration Period: June 1st - Jun 22nd Registration Method: Google Form Programme at a glance July 17th (Wed) - The Meeting of Humanities and Technology: The Beginning of Fusion (인문학과 기술의 만남: 융합의 시작) July 18th (Thu) - Basic Theory of Digital Humanities: Concepts and History (디지털 인문학 기초 이론: 개념과 역사) July 19th (Fri) - From Text to Data: New Ways to Read Humanities Texts in the Digital Age (텍스트에서 데이터로 : 디지털 시대 인문학 텍스트를 읽는 새로운 방법) July 22nd (Mon) - Digital Humanities and Visualization: The Importance and Key Examples of Information Visualization (디지털 인문학과 시각화: 정보 시각화의 중요성과 주요 사례) July 23rd (Tue) - Major Research Cases of Digital Humanities Abroad: Development Process and Implications (해외 디지털 인문학 주요 연구 사례: 해외 디지털 인문학 연구의 발전 과정과 시사점) July 24th (Wed) - Current Status of Digital Humanities Research in Korea: Latest Trends in Digital Humanities Departments and Institutes at Domestic Universities (국내 디지털 인문학 연구의 현주소: 국내 대학 디지털 인문학 학과 및 연구소의 최신 연구 동향) July 25th (Thu) - Utilizing Digital Analysis Tools for Humanities Data Analysis I: Cultural History Research Using Google’s N-gram Viewer (인문학 데이터 분석을 위한 디지털 분석 도구 활용 I: 구글의 N-gram Viewer를 활용한 문화사 연구) July 26th (Fri) - Utilizing Digital Analysis Tools for Humanities Data Analysis II: Psychological Analysis Using Linguistic Inquiry and Word Count (LIWC) (인문학 데이터 분석을 위한 디지털 분석 도구 활용 II: Linguistic Inquiry and Word Count (LIWC)를 활용한 심리 분석) July 29th (Mon) - Utilizing Digital Analysis Tools for Humanities Data Analysis III: Keyword Analysis Using the Web-based Analysis Platform ‘Voyant’ (인문학 데이터 분석을 위한 디지털 분석 도구 활용 III: 웹 기반 분석 플랫폼 ‘Voyant’를 활용한 주제어 분석) July 30th (Tue) - Digital Humanities and Social Network Analysis: Basic Theory of Social Networks (디지털 인문학과 소셜 네트워크 분석: 소셜 네트워크 기초 이론) July 31st (Wed) - Utilizing Digital Analysis Tools for Humanities Data Analysis IV: Social Network Analysis Using Gephi (인문학 데이터 분석을 위한 디지털 분석 도구 활용 IV: Gephi를 활용한 소셜 네트워크 분석)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jin Woo Jeong, Min Seo Kim, and Jinho Seo won the Encouragement Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on Data Analytics</title><link href="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-min-seo-kim-and-jinho-seo-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-data-analytics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jin Woo Jeong, Min Seo Kim, and Jinho Seo won the Encouragement Award in the 2024 CUK Competition on Data Analytics"/><published>2024-05-20T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-20T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-min-seo-kim-and-jinho-seo-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-data-analytics</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://o-jounlee.github.io/blog/2024/jin-woo-jeong-min-seo-kim-and-jinho-seo-won-the-encouragement-award-in-the-2024-cuk-competition-on-data-analytics/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The undergraduate research assistants of NS Lab@CUK have once again distinguished themselves in the 2024 CUK Competition on Data Analytics (제4회 가톨릭대학교 데이터분석 경진대회), securing the encouragement award for the third consecutive year. Jin Woo Jeong, Min Seo Kim, and Jinho Seo developed a model for detecting defects in PCB (Printed Circuit Board) manufacturing by modifying ResNet.]]></summary></entry></feed>